A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (A-K) FA1783
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Community and National Initiatives, 1999-2019; 1; 25.44 Cubic Feet 67 letter document boxes
  - LAB Miami - Learn, Act, Build Together (2014-48460), 2012-2014 (Box 69, Folder 978)
- Journalism and Media Innovation, 2003-2018; 2; 17.47 Cubic Feet 46 document boxes
  The Journalism and Media Innovation program focuses on protecting freedom of the press and free speech, as well as advancing methods of journalism that impact local media, and promotes talent, leadership, and technology innovation.
  - 100 Reporters - Double Exposure: Investigative Film Festival and Symposium (2016-52886), 2016-2018 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 596 Acres - Living Lots (2013-45552), 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Accrediting Council on Education in Journalism and Mass Communications - Database (2015-50942), 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - AL DIA Foundation - Temple University Placement in the Multilingual AL DIA Newsroom (2014-48971), 2014-2016 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science - SciLine (2017-54660) (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - American Council on Education - Convening Series on Campus Inclusion and Free Expression (2017-54043) (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - American Press Institute, Inc. - API Innovation Accelerator Project (2016-53556), 2017 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    Advance innovation, best practices, and shared resources for news publishers on data, metrics, and business sustainability models.
  - American Press Institute, Inc. - Newsroom Study on Digital Tools and Technology (2014-48927), 2012-2014 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - American Press Institute, Inc. - Ethics of Non-Proft Journalism Funding (2014-50010), 2015 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - American Society of News Editors Foundation, Inc. - ASNE Emerging Leaders Program and Diversity Survey (2017-53851) (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - American Society of News Editors Foundation, Inc. - 2016 ASNE Diversity Program (2016-52260), 2014-2017 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - American Society of News Editors Foundation, Inc. - Minority Leadership Institutes (2015-51048) (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - American Society of News Editors Foundation, Inc. - Digital Outreach Initiative (2014-49406), 2012-2014 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - American Society of News Editors Foundation, Inc. - Free to Tweet II Campaign to Increase Awareness of the First Amendment (2012-3617), 2011-2014 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - The American University - Game Design in the Newsroom (2016-52089), 2015-2016 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - The American University - JoLT Fellowships (2014-49455), 2012-2014 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    Leadership-building program with a focus in game design and systems thinking to develop media leaders.
  - Amplify Labs, Inc. - LocalData (2012-2222), 2011-2014 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Arizona State University Foundation - Reinventing Local TV News (2017-53820), 2015-2017 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Arizona State University Foundation - Newsgeist (2017-54648) (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Arizona State University Foundation - Newsgeist (2015-50636), 2015-2016 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Arizona State University Foundation - Knight-Cronkite School Alumni Innovation Grants to Support Digital Reporting and Storytelling (2014-49068), 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Arizona State University Foundation - Public Insight Network (PIN) Bureau at ASU (2013-47148), 2011-2015 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Arizona State University Foundation - Experimental News 21 Student Reporting Project (2008-0076) (2008-0709), 2008-2012 (Box 8, Folder 113-115)
  - Asian American Journalists Association - Executive Leadership Program (2015-51087), 2015-2016 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Asian American Journalists Association - Innovation Alley Conference Sponsorship (2014-49131) (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - The Aspen Institute Inc. - Knight Commission on Trust, Media, and Democracy (2017-54086), 2015-2017 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - The Aspen Institute Inc. - Forum on Communication and Society, Open Government Theme (2013-42784), 2011-2014 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - The Associated Press - AP Fact Check (2017-53838) (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Associated Press Sports Editors (APSE), Miami Foundation - Diversity Fellowship Program (2016-52523), 2013-2016 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - The Associated Press - Voter Information Accuracy through Researching Nonpartisan Exit Polling Alternatives (2015-51012), 2013-2015 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - The Associated Press - Data Services Team (2015-51244), 2013-2017 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - The Associated Press - Software Tool to Combine Datasets Based on Geographic Information (2013-42768), 2010-2013 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - The Associated Press - Software Tool to Find Stories in Large Datasets (2011-0278), 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Association for Education in Journalism and Mass Communication - Knight News Challenge (2011-0099), 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Association for Education in Journalism and Mass Communication - Journalism Administrator and Teachers of the Year Awards (2003-0205), 2003-2006 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - The Atlantic Monthly Group, Inc. - Quartz Bot Studio (2016-53089), 2016-2017 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - Jim Bettinger Challenge Fund for Newsroom Innovation (2016-52769), 2016-2017 (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - Stanford Knight Fellows (2014-49421), 2013-2014 (Box 15, Folder 210)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - JSK Journalism Fellows (2014-50043), 2012-2016 (Box 15, Folder 212)
  - Brown Bag Software LLC - Game-Like Simulation App to Model Transit and Land-Use Programs (2013-47661), 2012-2013 (Box 17, Folder 238)
  - CALmatters - State Politics and Policy Grant (2015-50804), 2014-2016 (Box 18, Folder 246)
  - Camden Coalition of Healthcare Providers - Camden Health Explorer Dashboard (2014-47976), 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 247)
  - Carey Institute for Global Good Inc. - Resident Fellows Program for Journalists Working on Long-form Narrative Projects (2015-51497), 2013-2016 (Box 18, Folder 250)
  - The Carole Kneeland Project for Responsible Television Journalism - 2018 and 2019 Conferences (2017-53883) (Box 18, Folder 253)
  - Center for Investigative Reporting - Umbel Analytics Tool (2013-47137), 2011-2013 (Box 20, Folder 270)
  - The Center for Michigan, Inc. - Detroit Journalism Cooperative: Bridge Magazine (2016-53483), 2015-2017 (Box 20, Folder 273)
  - The Center for Michigan, Inc. - Solutions Journalism: Detroit/Michigan (2013-47495), 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 274)
  - The Center for Public Integrity - Data Journalism Transformation Project (2016-52454), 2014-2016 (Box 20, Folder 275)
  - Chaki Ng - Whilecard (2014-48431), 2012-2014 (Box 21, Folder 288)
    A prototype of an activity-based news recommender system.
  - Chalkbeat Inc. - Chalkbeat Detroit (2016-53583) (Box 21, Folder 289)
  - Smart Chicago Collaborative - Foodborne Chicago (2013-47651), 2011-2014 (Box 22, Folder 304)
  - Chicago Public Library Foundation - Hotspot at Home Program (2014-49389), 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 310)
  - CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - Knight-CUNY Internships (2014-49136), 2013-2016 (Box 26, Folder 374)
  - CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - Knight-CUNY Internships (2017-54622) (Box 26, Folder 369)
  - CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - Tow-Knight Center for Entrepreneurial Journalism (2010-2308), 2008-2014 (Box 26, Folder 375-376)
  - CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - Tow-Knight Center for Entrepreneurial Journalism (2016-53101), 2014-2017 (Box 26, Folder 370)
  - CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - Knight-Vice Innovators Fund (2015-50627), 2014-2017 (Box 26, Folder 371)
  - CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - Knight Innovation Awards (2014-49060), 2013-2016 (Box 26, Folder 373)
  - Civic Industries - Civic Insight (2014-48470), 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 377)
    A tool for managing property records and opening data about properties to the public.
  - Civic Hall - Post-Election Gathering (2016-53236), 2013-2016 (Box 27, Folder 378)
  - Civic Ninjas - Sitegeist Health Prototype (2013-47636), 2012-2013 (Box 27, Folder 382)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists Inc. - Matching Grant (2016-52316), 2014-2016 (Box 28, Folder 404)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists Inc. - Matching Grant (2016-53422), 2015-2016 (Box 28, Folder 405)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists Inc. - Matching Gift Project (2017-55255) (Box 28, Folder 406)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists Inc. - Interactive Databases (2014-49252), 2013-2016 (Box 29, Folder 407)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists Inc. - Matching Grant for the 23rd CPJ Awards Ceremony Dinner (2013-47650), 2012-2014 (Box 29, Folder 411)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Detroit Journalism Cooperative: Detroit Local Journalism Engagement Fund (2016-53367), 2014-2017 (Box 29, Folder 422)
  - Community Foundation of New Jersey - NJ Spotlight, Knight Local Media Initiative (2014-47998), 2011-2015 (Box 33, Folder 454)
  - Community Foundation of New Jersey - NJ Spotlight, Knight Community Information Challenge (2012-0145), 2010-2014 (Box 33, Folder 455)
  - Hollaback - Pilot of a Mobile Application to Report Street Harassment (2013-42783), 2010-2013 (Box 62, Folder 868)
  - Community Initiatives - Intergenerational Fellowship in Digital Journalism (2015-51287) (Box 35, Folder 470)
  - Connecticut Public Broadcasting Inc. - The People Project (2017-53863) (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - The Conversation US Inc. - Audience Development Coordinator (2015-51194), 2015-2016 (Box 36, Folder 484)
  - The Corporation of Mercer University - Enhancements to Collaborative Journalism Center (2015-50404), 2012-2017 (Box 36, Folder 493)
  - The Corporation of Mercer University - Center for Collaborative Journalism (2017-54124), 2016-2017 (Box 36, Folder 494)
  - Cortico Corporation - Trusted Networks (2017-54604) (Box 37, Folder 496)
  - CultureWorks Greater Philadelphia - Mobile Journalism Guide (2015-51851), 2015-2016 (Box 39, Folder 532)
  - Curators of the University of Missouri - Trusting News Project (2017-54837) (Box 39, Folder 534)
  - Curators of the University of Missouri - Measuring Noise Pollution with Arduino (2013-47617), 2013-2014 (Box 39, Folder 535)
  - DailyChatter LLC - University Program (2017-54908) (Box 39, Folder 541)
  - Democracy Works - TurboVote (2012-0055), 2010-2012 (Box 41, Folder 558)
  - Detroit Educational Television Foundation - Detroit Journalism Cooperative: Detroit Public Television (2016-53471), 2016-2017 (Box 41, Folder 568)
  - Detroit Educational Television Foundation - Detroit Journalism Cooperative (2014-50241), 2014-2016 (Box 41, Folder 569)
  - Digital Democracy - Mobile Toolkit (2012-0406), 2011-2013 (Box 43, Folder 587)
  - Drexel University - Philadelphia Daily News Partnership for Non-Profit Arts Journalism (2012-0107) (Box 45, Folder 617)
  - Duke University - Trust and News Initiative: Automating Fact-Checking (2017-53747) (Box 45, Folder 618)
  - Duke University - Media and Philanthropy (2014-49582), 2012-2014 (Box 45, Folder 619)
  - Evenly Distributed LLC - LibraryBox (2014-48717), 2014-2016 (Box 47, Folder 651)
  - Farmers Market Coalition - Market Metrics (2013-47595) (Box 48, Folder 665)
  - FireWorks Film LLC - Data Docs (2013-46319), 2011-2013 (Box 49, Folder 673)
  - Florida International University Foundation Inc. - Expanding Online Education (2014-49620), 2013-2016 (Box 49, Folder 683)
  - Florida International University Foundation Inc. - Knight Innovator in Residence (2013-47141), 2012-2015 (Box 49, Folder 686)
  - Forest Giant - LouLoops (2013-47679), 2013-2014 (Box 50, Folder 698)
    Mobile app for bicycle route mapping.
  - Foundation for Minority Interests in Media - Diversity Pipeline for Local TV News (2017-53824) (Box 53, Folder 725)
  - Front Porch Forum - Open Source Software for Neighborhood News (2010-0231), 2010-2012 (Box 54, Folder 752)
  - Front Porch Forum - Program Related Investment (2010-0231) (Box 54, Folder 752)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Global Editors Network, International Center for Journalists - 2018 and 2019 Data Journalism Awards (2017-54989), 2015-2017 (Box 57, Folder 793)
  - Global Editors Network - Sustainability Plan (2014-48259), 2012-2015 (Box 57, Folder 794)
  - Global Editors Network, International Center for Journalists - 2016 and 2017 Data Journalism Awards (2015-51968), 2015-2016 (Box 58, Folder 795)
  - Globe Newspaper Company, Inc. - Newsroom Innovation between The Boston Globe and the MIT Center for Civic Media (2012-0259), 2012-2017 (Box 58, Folder 796)
  - Globe Newspaper Company, Inc. - The Boston Globe and EveryBlock.com (2010-0085), 2009-2010 (Box 58, Folder 797)
  - GovLoop - GovLoop Academy Courses on Open Data and Civic Engagement (2014-48447), 2012-2014 (Box 58, Folder 803)
  - The Greater Washington Educational Telecommunications Association - Race Matters (2015-51730), 2012-2015 (Box 59, Folder 832)
  - GreenInfo Network - Get Outside (2013-46306), 2011-2013 (Box 60, Folder 833)
    Parks and recreation mapping application.
  - The GroundTruth Project - Crossing the Divide (2017-54343) (Box 60, Folder 834)
  - Guardian News and Media LLC - Mobile Team (2014-49928), 2014-2016 (Box 60, Folder 835)
  - Hampton University - Center for Digital Media Innovation (2013-47926), 2012-2015 (Box 60, Folder 844)
  - Hechinger Report, Teachers College Columbia University - Single Topic News Project (2016-53717) (Box 60, Folder 849)
  - Hypothes.is - Hyposthes.is [Hypothesis] (2012-3527), 2011-2014 (Box 62, Folder 877)
    Open source tool and community for annotating content across the internet.
  - Ida B. Wells Society for Investigative Reporting, CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - Ida B. Wells Society for Investigative Reporting (2016-53419) (Box 62, Folder 879)
  - IDEO - Knight Foundation-Branded Implementation of openIDEO Platform for Running Contests and Idea Challenges (2012-0116), 2010-2012 (Box 62, Folder 882)
  - Institute for Nonprofit News - News Match 2017 (2017-54643) (Box 64, Folder 898)
  - Institute for Nonprofit News - Training and Digital Hub Project (2016-53400), 2015-2016 (Box 64, Folder 899)
  - Institute for Nonprofit News - Local Media Initiative (2013-47899), 2012-2015 (Box 64, Folder 900)
  - Institute on Higher Awesome Studies, Inc. - Micro-Grants Organization (2011-0236), 2010-2014 (Box 64, Folder 906)
  - International Center for Journalists - Cuban Journalism Fellowships (2015-51612), 2015-2016 (Box 64, Folder 908)
  - International Center for Journalists - Knight International Journalism Fellowships (2015-51333), 2013-2017 (Box 65, Folder 909)
  - International Center for Journalists - African News Innovation Challenge 2014 (2014-48154), 2012-2014 (Box 65, Folder 910)
  - International Center for Journalists - United States-Russian Young Journalists Exchange Program (2011-0214), 2009-2012 (Box 65, Folder 911)
  - International Center for Journalists - International Media Institute of India (2011-0080), 2008-2013 (Box 65, Folder 912)
  - International Center for New Media, Austria - Millennium Development Goals Contest (2010-0051), 2007-2012 (Box 65, Folder 913)
  - International House - The Diverse Future (2016-53403), 2016-2017 (Box 65, Folder 915)
  - International Senior Lawyers Project - Espionage Act of 1917 White Paper (2017-54893) (Box 65, Folder 917)
  - Investigative Reporters and Editors Inc. - Knight Network at Annual Conferences (2016-53202) (Box 66, Folder 924)
  - Investigative Reporters and Editors Inc. - IRE TV Watchdog Network (2017-54112), 2015-2017 (Box 66, Folder 925)
  - Investigative Reporters and Editors Inc. - Knight Innovation Initiative (2013-47903), 2012-2015 (Box 66, Folder 926)
  - Investigative Reporters and Editors Inc. - DocumentCloud (2014-48698), 2012-2015 (Box 66, Folder 928)
  - Investigative Reporters and Editors Inc. - Census.IRE.org (2012-0320), 2010-2014 (Box 66, Folder 929)
  - Investigative Reporters and Editors Inc. - Newsroom Data Application (2011-0239), 2009-2013 (Box 66, Folder 930)
  - Jefferson Center for New Democratic Processes - Your Voice Ohio (2017-53935) (Box 67, Folder 938)
  - Jefferson Institute - Platform for Research of Online Discussions (PROD) (2013-46959), 2012-2014 (Box 67, Folder 942)
  - John S. Knight Memorial Journalism Fund Corporation - Scholarships (2014-48321), 2012-2014 (Box 67, Folder 946)
  - Journalism Development Network - Who are the Gatekeepers? (2014-49533), 2013-2014 (Box 68, Folder 958)
    Project to examine Eastern Europe's digital infrastructure.
  - Kent State University Foundation - Poynter KSU Media Ethics Workshop (2015-50605), 2015-2016 (Box 69, Folder 969)
  - KQED Inc. - Deep Look Audience Engagement (2015-50497) (Box 69, Folder 975)
  - KQED Inc. - NPR "Project Carbon" (2015-51360), 2014-2015 (Box 69, Folder 976)
  - KQED Inc. - Uncovering Cost, Examining Impact (2014-48409) (Box 69, Folder 977)
- Arts, 2007-2019; 3; 21.65 Cubic Feet 57 letter document boxes
  The Knight Arts program awards grants that promote authenticity and inclusion, development of talent and organizations, and transformation. This series also contains grants that fall under the Knight Arts Challenge in which the grants awarded must focus on the arts, take place in or benefit South Florida, and the awardees much match the amount granted by the Knight Foundation.
  - 100 Words Film Festival - Third Annual Film Festival (2016-52713), 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The 567 Center for Renewal - Lost Keys Literary Festival (2016-52722) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Actors' Playhouse Productions, Inc., Miami - Miami-Dade School Trip to "In the Heights" and Rap-Writing Contest, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-0370), 2012-2014 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Actors' Playhouse Productions, Inc., Miami - Actors Playhouse at the Miracle Theatre "In the Heights" PSA DVD Video, Knight Arts Challenge (2012-1444) (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  - Actor's Theatre of Charlotte - Dual Perspectives (2016-52692), 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - African American Museum, Philadelphia - RAAMP It Up Wednesdays, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0042), 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center, Inc. - Gantt Center for African American Arts and Culture Operating Support (2017-54466), 2017-2019 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center, Inc. - Inside Out Charlotte - Gannt (2016-53444), 2016-2018 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Akron Art Museum - Operating Funds (2017-54366) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Akron Art Museum - #WatchUsGrowAkron [Watch Us Grow Akron] (2016-52741) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Akron Art Museum - Inside Out Akron (2014-49554), 2014-2016 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Akron Art Museum - Inside Out Akron (2016-53386), 2017 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Alyans Atizay Ayisyn, Inc. - dba Haitian Cultural Arts Alliance, Knight Arts Challenge (2017-55393), 2017-2018 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Al-Bustan Seeds of Culture - Music Concert Series Featuring Al-Bustan Takht Ensemble (2014-49994), 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Al-Bustan Seeds of Culture - Arab Music Concert Series Featuring Federico Garcia Lorca (2013-47042), 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Al-Bustan Seeds of Culture - Arab Music Concert Series, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0043), 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - American Alliance of Museums - In Conversation: Future Thinking about Museums and Technology (2017-55117), 2018 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - American Documentary, Inc. - Knight AmDoc Kickstarter Patron Fund (2017-55155) (Box 5, Folder 69)
    Crowdfunding to support nonfiction projects and filmmakers directly connected to Knight communities.
  - American Friends of Un Techo Para Mi Pais, Inc. - ARTecho (2013-47765), 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - American Friends of Un Techo Para Mi Pais, Inc. - ARTecho (2012-2127), 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Americans for the Arts - Knight Fellows Program and the Emerging Leaders Preconference, San Antonio, Texas (2012-1776), 2010-2013 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Ampersand Guild - Heartbeat of Macon: Supporting Macon Artists (2017-54963) (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Anaphiel Foundation, Inc. - Miami Design District Performance Series (2017-54944) (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Andreas H. Bechtler Arts Foundation - Community Outreach, Access and Inclusion (2016-52680), 2016-2017 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Andreas H. Bechtler Arts Foundation - Inside Out Charlotte - Bechtler (2016-53443), 2016-2017 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - ArtPop - #ArtPopCLT Charlotte (2016-52648) (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Artrain Inc. - CriticCar Detroit (2014-4936) (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Arts and Science Council Charlotte Mecklenburg, Inc. - Learning Community Cohort (2016-53257), 2016-2017 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Arts and Science Council Charlotte Mecklenburg, Inc. - Sphinx Virtuosi Master Classes (2015-50662), 2015-2016 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Arts and Business Council of Greater Philadelphia - Designing Leadership Program (2012-2837), 2011-2015 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - ArtSi Charlotte - "Cafecito with ArtSi" Networking Events, "Con A de Arte" Latino Art Exhibition (2015-50635), 2016-2017 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Arts for Learning, Miami - Summer Art Internships and Apprenticeships for High-School Students (2012-0373), 2010-2015 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Asian Arts Initiative - "Salt Soul" by Jungwoong Kim (2016-52710) (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Asian Arts Initiative - Artistic Experiences in Chinatown and South Philadelphia (2012-0069), 2009-2013 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc. - ArtistYear Program Meetings, Philadelphia and St. Paul (2015-50609), 2015-2016 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Association for Public Art - "Fireflies" Exhibit by Cai Guo-Qiang (2016-53082) (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Astral Artistic Services - Distinctive Voices: Celebrating Cultural Influences in Classical Music (2011-0044), 2009-2012 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Backwater Arts, LLC - Anne and Mark's Art Party (2014-48929) (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - BalletX, The Miami Foundation - Keepers of the Art Music Showcase and "Teen Forum" (2013-46703), 2011-2013 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Bearded Ladies Cabaret, Painted Bride Art Center - The Poison Cookie (2017-54801) (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - The Betsy Hotel - Writer-in-Residence Program, Miami Beach (2012-0458), 2011-2014 (Box 12, Folder 171)
  - Bibb County - Macon-Bibb County Parks and Recreation Free Film Screenings (2013-47616), 2012-2013 (Box 12, Folder 175)
  - The Big House Foundation, Inc. - Museum Music Story Teller Series (2016-52723), 2016-2017 (Box 12, Folder 177)
  - Black Lily, Inc. - 2017 BlackStar Film Festival (2017-54351) (Box 14, Folder 185)
  - Black Lily, Inc. - 2016 BlackStar Film Festival (2016-52662) (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - Black Pearl Chamber Orchestra - Synaesthesia (2016-52674) (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - Black Pearl Chamber Orchestra - ¡Conduct!, Knight Arts Challenge (2011-0047), 2009-2012 (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - BlackStar Film Festival - African Diaspora Cinema (2012-2616), 2011-2014 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - Borscht Film Festival - CCCV Stories: Redefining Miami in Film, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0253), 2007-2012 (Box 16, Folder 213)